Guide to the William Saroyan Papers, 1926-1981
Department of Special Collections
- Manuscripts, 1928-1981., Series 5
  - Plays, Subseries 5.02
    - Play [#2]: TS,1973 (Carton 55, Folder 26)
    - Play: TS,1977 (Carton 55, Folder 27)
    - The Play: TS,1949 (Carton 55, Folder 28)
    - The Play at the O.K.: TS, corrected,1949 (Carton 55, Folder 29)
    - The Play of Ideas: TS,1952 (Carton 55, Folder 30)
    - The Politzky Surprise: TS, corrected,1950 (Carton 55, Folder 31)
    - The Politzky Surprise: TS carbons, 2 copies,1950 (Carton 55, Folder 32)
    - The Politzky Surprise: Titled "World Failure at the Candy Store, or The Politzky Surprise," TS carbon ,n.d. (Carton 55, Folder 33)
    - The Politzky Surprise: Titled "World Failure at the Candy Store," corrected,n.d. (Carton 55, Folder 34)
    - Poor Things: TS; photocopy,1974 (Carton 55, Folder 35)
    - Profit and Loss: Adaptation of "Tehin-Tehin," by Francois Billetdoux, TS, corrected,1960 (Carton 55, Folder 36)
    - Propositions: TS,1972 (Carton 55, Folder 37)
    - Propositions: TS, corrected,1972 (Carton 55, Folder 38)
    - Propositions: Mimeo TS,1979 (Carton 55, Folder 39)
    - The Psychiatrists: TS,1975 (Carton 55, Folder 40)
    - The Real World. A Dance-Play: TS; TS carbon,1956 (Carton 55, Folder 41)
    - The Real World. A Dance-Play: Titled "The Light-Footed Lunatic," and "The Crazy Waiter," TS, corrected,1955 (Carton 55, Folder 42)
    - The Real World. A Dance-Play: Titled "The Exceptional Children," TS, corrected,1955 (Carton 55, Folder 43)
    - The Real World. A Dance-Play: Titled "The Crazy Waiter or The Exceptional Children," TS carbon ,n.d. (Carton 55, Folder 44)
    - The Rebirth Celebration of the Human Race at Artie Zabala's Off-Broadway Theater: Original TS, titled,1970 (Carton 56, Folder 1)
    - The Rebirth Celebration of the Human Race at Artie Zabala's Off-Broadway Theater: Mimeo TSS-2 (Carton 56, Folder 2)
    - The Rebirth Celebration of the Human Race at Artie Zabala's Off-Broadway Theater: Misc.,1975 (Carton 56, Folder 3)
    - The Rudolph Valentino Tango: TS,1974 (Carton 56, Folder 4)
    - Sam Ego's House: TS, corrected,1947 (Carton 56, Folder 5)
    - Sam Ego's House: TS; carbon TS, corrected,1947 (Carton 56, Folder 6)
    - Sam Ego's House: Titled "Sam Ego's House or Angels Aghast," TS, 2 copies,1947 (Carton 56, Folder 7)
    - Sam Ego's House: TS, corrected,1948 (Carton 56, Folder 8)
    - Sam Ego's House: Misc.,1949 (Carton 56, Folder 9)
    - Sam the Highest Jumper of Them All: Titled "Sam Harkharkalark's Horror at the Dreadful News," TS; mimeo TS,1974 (Carton 56, Folder 10)
    - Sam the Highest Jumper of Them All: Intro. and misc. notes,1960 (Carton 56, Folder 11)
    - Sam the Highest Jumper of Them All: Galleys, corrected, 2 sets,1961 (Carton 56, Folder 12)
    - Sam the Highest Jumper of Them All: Page proofs, 2 copies,1961 (Carton 56, Folder 13)
    - Sam the Highest Jumper of Them All: Song galleys,1961 (Carton 56, Folder 14)
    - The Sandwich Eaters: TS carbon, corrected,1963 (Carton 56, Folder 15)
    - Scalawag's Heaven: TS, corrected,1952 (Carton 56, Folder 16)
    - Scalawag's Heaven: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 56, Folder 17)
    - Scalawag's Heaven: Omnibus script, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 56, Folder 18)
    - Scalawag's Heaven: Omnibus script, corrected,n.d. (Carton 56, Folder 19)
    - Scalawag's Heaven: Omnibus script, revised,n.d. (Carton 56, Folder 20)
    - The Screams of the Famous People of 47th St.: Titled "The Famous People of 47th St.," TS, corrected, 1970 (Carton 56, Folder 21)
    - The Screams of the Famous People of 47th St.: Mimeo TS,1971 (Carton 56, Folder 22)
    - See the Man See Him Try. Poor, Poor Man. See Him Cry.: TS,1974 (Carton 56, Folder 23)
    - Sensible Sermon: TS,1975 (Carton 56, Folder 24)
    - Settled Out of Court: Mimeo TS, corrected,1959 (Carton 56, Folder 25)
    - Settled Out of Court: Mimeo TS,1959 (Carton 56, Folder 26)
    - Settled Out of Court: Proofs,1962 (Carton 56, Folder 27)
    - The Shepherd or The New York Comedy: TS, corrected,1960 (Carton 56, Folder 28)
    - The Ship's Company: TS carbon,1941 (Carton 56, Folder 29)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Agreement,1956 (Carton 56, Folder 30)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Galleys,1952 (Carton 56, Folder 31)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Tearsheet,1952 (Carton 56, Folder 32)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Titled "Mr. Crookshank's World," TS, corrected,1950 (Carton 56, Folder 33)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: TS carbon, corrected,1950 (Carton 56, Folder 34)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: TS, corrected, n.d. (Carton 56, Folder 35)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: TS,n.d. (Carton 56, Folder 36)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Notes,1956 (Carton 56, Folder 37)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Dutch TS carbon,1957 (Carton 56, Folder 38)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Mimeo TS; misc.,1957 (Carton 56, Folder 39)
    - The Slaughter of the Innocents: Hebrew Translation,1957 (Carton 56, Folder 40)
    - Sleeping: TS,1978 (Carton 56, Folder 41)
    - Sleeping: TS photocopy,1978 (Carton 56, Folder 42)
    - The Sleeping Beauty of Highway 99: TS carbon, corrected,1950 (Carton 56, Folder 43)
    - The Sleeping Beauty of Highway 99: TS carbon, corrected,1957 (Carton 56, Folder 44)
    - Slooley's Portrait: TS carbon, corrected,1957 (Carton 56, Folder 45)
    - Somebody and Somebody Else: Titled "Anybody and Anybody Else," TS,1974 (Carton 56, Folder 46)
    - Something About a Soldier: TS, corrected,1939 (Carton 57, Folder 1)
    - Something About a Soldier: TS, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 2)
    - Something About a Soldier: Matson TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 3)
    - Something About a Soldier: Notes,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 4)
    - Something About a Soldier: Publicity; programs,1940 (Carton 57, Folder 5)
    - Sometimes I Ask Myself What is the Moon: TS, corrected,1969 (Carton 57, Folder 6)
    - A Special Announcement: Galley,1940 (Carton 57, Folder 7)
    - A Spring Day at the Marriage License Bureau: TS, corrected,1952 (Carton 57, Folder 8)
    - A Spring Day at the Marriage License Bureau: Omnibus TS carbons, corrected, 2 copies,1952 (Carton 57, Folder 9)
    - A Spring Day at the Marriage License Bureau: Titled "The Marriage License," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 10)
    - A Spring Day at the Marriage License Bureau: Omnibus TS carbon,1952 (Carton 57, Folder 11)
    - A Spring Day at the Marriage License Bureau: Titled "Two or Three Marriages," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 12)
    - A Spring Day at the Marriage License Bureau: Titled "A Midsummer Daydream," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 13)
    - Stonehenge in Disarray: TS,1974 (Carton 57, Folder 14)
    - Stonehill: TS; TS photocopy,1974 (Carton 57, Folder 15)
    - Subway Circus: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 16)
    - Subway Circus: TS carbons, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 17)
    - Subway Circus: Page proofs,1940 (Carton 57, Folder 18)
    - Subway Circus: Adaptation for Screen & Television by Herbert Gehr, mimeo TS,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 19)
    - Sweeney in the Trees: TS, corrected,1939 (Carton 57, Folder 20)
    - Sweeney in the Trees: TS carbon, corrected,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 21)
    - Sweeney in the Trees: TS, corrected,1940 (Carton 57, Folder 22)
    - Sweeney in the Trees: Misc. notes,1939 (Carton 57, Folder 23)
    - Tales from the Vienna Streets: TS, corrected,1980 (Carton 57, Folder 24)
    - Talking to You: TS, 3 copies,1941 (Carton 57, Folder 25)
    - Talking to You and Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: Letter, notes on New York production,1961 (Carton 57, Folder 26)
    - Talking to You and Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: Mimeo script, annotated,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 27)
    - The Television Impeachment of the Boy President's Assassin's Financial Backer: TS; tearsheet,1974 (Carton 57, Folder 28)
    - The Thanksgiving Day Indian: TS, 3 copies,1953 (Carton 57, Folder 29)
    - There They Go Again: Anybody and Everybody Else: TS photocopy,1974 (Carton 57, Folder 30)
    - The Time of Your Life: TS orig.; Changes, corrections; TS carbon, revision (in box),1939 (Carton 57, Folder 31)
    - The Time of Your Life: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 32)
    - The Time of Your Life: Anthology tearsheets,1939 (Carton 57, Folder 33)
    - The Time of Your Life: Misc. notes,1939 (Carton 57, Folder 34)
    - The Time of Your Life: Circle Theatre program,n.d. (Carton 57, Folder 35)
    - The Time of Your Life: French translation,1949 (Carton 57, Folder 36)
    - The Time of Your Life: Rewritten scenes,1954 (Carton 57, Folder 37)
    - The Time of Your Life: TS, 3 copies,1954 (Carton 57, Folder 38)
    - The Time of Your Life: TS carbon,1954 (Carton 57, Folder 39)
    - The Time of Your Life: Misc. notes and revisions,1954 (Carton 58, Folder 1)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Galleys, p. 1-170 annotated,1966 (Carton 58, Folder 2)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Galleys, p. 171-344, annotated,1966 (Carton 58, Folder 3)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Galleys, "marked set",1966 (Carton 58, Folder 4)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Galleys, annotated,1966 (Carton 58, Folder 5)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Galleys for Bantam Ed.,1966 (Carton 58, Folder 6)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Galleys, "Author's Set," corrected,1966 (Carton 58, Folder 7)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Misc. front matter,1966 (Carton 58, Folder 8)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Misc. front matter,1967 (Carton 58, Folder 9)
    - The Time of Your Life and Other Plays: Revised Credo,1968 (Carton 58, Folder 10)
    - The Tragedy of Ben Marcus: TS, corrected,1940 (Carton 58, Folder 11)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," introduction TS and TS carbon; galleys; notes ,n.d. (Carton 58, Folder 12)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," TS; corrected TS carbon,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 13)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "On the Banks of the Wabash," TS carbon,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 14)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Misc. correspondence; notes,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 15)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," first revise, corrected,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 16)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," 2nd and 3rd revise,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 17)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," TS, 2 copies,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 18)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," 3rd revise, corrected,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 19)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," 3rd revise, edited,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 20)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," 4th revise, edited and corrected,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 21)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "A Nice Day for a Picnic," TS; TS carbon,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 22)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "Death Along the Wabash," TS, corrected,1961 (Carton 58, Folder 23)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: TS, 2 copies,1961 (Carton 59, Folder 1)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Notes, etc.,1961 (Carton 59, Folder 2)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: TS, corrected,1962 (Carton 59, Folder 3)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: TS,1962 (Carton 59, Folder 4)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "The Getaway," French translation, TS carbon,1967 (Carton 59, Folder 5)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Titled "High Time Along the Wabash," Act 2, Scene 2, TS, corrected,1961 (Carton 59, Folder 6)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: Programs, souvenirs, etc.,1961 (Carton 59, Folder 7)
    - Trash Along the Wabash: TS, annotated and corrected,1975 (Carton 59, Folder 8)
    - The Travelers: TS, corrected,1937 (Carton 59, Folder 9)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Outline; notes,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 10)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 11)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Titled "The Outskirts of Heaven," TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 12)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Titled "Ah, San Francisco," TS, corrected,1954 (Carton 59, Folder 13)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Titled "Ah, San Francisco," notes,1954 (Carton 59, Folder 14)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Titled "Ah, San Francisco," misc.,1954 (Carton 59, Folder 15)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Titled "Love in San Francisco," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 16)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Titled "Love in San Francisco," TS carbon, corrected,1954 (Carton 59, Folder 17)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: Photocopy,1963 (Carton 59, Folder 18)
    - The Trombone Player, or Love in San Francisco: TS,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 19)
    - Turks in the World: TS,1975 (Carton 59, Folder 20)
    - The Unknown Playwright's Unwritten Play: TS carbon, corrected,1956 (Carton 59, Folder 21)
    - The Unknown Playwright's Unwritten Play: TS carbon, corrected,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 22)
    - The Unstoppable Gray Fox: TS; TS carbon, annotated; notes,1961 (Carton 59, Folder 23)
    - The Unstoppable Gray Fox: GE Theater script,1961 (Carton 59, Folder 24)
    - The Unstoppable Gray Fox: Titled "The Hundred and One Years of the Gray Fox," TS, corrected; TS carbon; notes,1961 (Carton 59, Folder 25)
    - The Unstoppable Gray Fox: TS; tearsheet,1962 (Carton 59, Folder 26)
    - A Very Short Christmas Play: TS, corrected; notes,1952 (Carton 59, Folder 27)
    - The Violin Messiah: TS carbon, corrected,1950 (Carton 59, Folder 28)
    - The Violin Messiah: TS, corrected,1950 (Carton 59, Folder 29)
    - Vive!: Mimeo script, annotated,1953 (Carton 59, Folder 30)
    - Vive!: Titled "The Survivors," Omnibus script,1952 (Carton 59, Folder 31)
    - Vive!: Titled "The Survivors," Omnibus TS,1952 (Carton 59, Folder 32)
    - Vive!: Titled "The Survivors," Omnibus TS carbon, corrected,1952 (Carton 59, Folder 33)
    - Vive!: Titled "The Survivors," Omnibus script,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 34)
    - Vive!: Titled "The Survivors," TS, corrected,1952 (Carton 59, Folder 35)
    - Vive!: Titled "To Paint a Paris Wall," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 59, Folder 36)
    - Warsaw Visitor: Titled "I Have Seen the Future, and It Works. Lincoln Steffens 1929. I Have Seen Everything and Nothing Works. William Saroyan. 1980," TS carbon,1980 (Carton 59, Folder 37)
    - The Weirdos: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1960 (Carton 59, Folder 38)
    - What You Haven't Got, You Get Along Without: TS,1974 (Carton 59, Folder 39)
    - The White Swans of the River Liffey: TS, 3 copies,1940 (Carton 59, Folder 40)
    - The Wild Pitch: TS carbon, corrected,1953 (Carton 59, Folder 41)
    - The Wild Pitch: TS, corrected, 2 copies; TS carbon,1953 (Carton 59, Folder 42)
    - Winners: (A One Week Play): TS,1974 (Carton 59, Folder 43)
    - The World and His Widow: TS,1975 (Carton 59, Folder 44)
    - The World and His Wild Wife: Titled "The World and His Wild Wicked Wonderful Eighth Wife," TS; photocopy,1974 (Carton 59, Folder 45)
    - The Worst Years of Our Lives: TS, corrected,1953 (Carton 59, Folder 46)
    - Yalp: TS, corrected; mimeo,1974 (Carton 59, Folder 47)
    - The Young Brothers Karamanaganian: TS,1975 (Carton 59, Folder 48)
    - The Young Lovers: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1955 (Carton 59, Folder 49)
  - Short Stories, Subseries 5.03
    - Me: Tearsheet; special edition printing,1963 (Oversize 1)
    - About a Man Who Wanted to Be In Love: Tearsheet photocopy,1928 (Carton 60, Folder 1)
    - The Accident at the County Fair: TS, corrected; TS carbons, 2 copies; galleys, corrected; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 60, Folder 2)
    - The Actor: Titled "The Girl Giggled," TS, corrected, 2 copies,1949 (Carton 60, Folder 3)
    - The Actress and the Cop: Titled "I Can't Grow Up" and "The Wife and Daughter of the Man from Iceland," TS, corrected,1956 (Carton 60, Folder 4)
    - The Actress and the Cop: Titled "The Wife and Daughter of the Man from Iceland," TS carbon, corrected,n.d. (Carton 60, Folder 5)
    - The Actress and the Cop: Titled "The Wife and Daughter of the Man from Iceland," TS carbons, corrected, 2 copies,1956 (Carton 60, Folder 6)
    - The Actress and the Cop: Titled "The Wife and Daughter of the Man from Iceland," TS carbons, corrected, 2 copies ,n.d. (Carton 60, Folder 7)
    - The Actress and the Cop: Misc.,1956 (Carton 60, Folder 8)
    - The Actress and the Cop: Tearsheets,1957 (Carton 60, Folder 9)
    - The Admirers of the Sun: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1950 (Carton 60, Folder 10)
    - The Admirers of the Sun: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1950 (Carton 60, Folder 11)
    - The Admirers of the Sun: Titled "Old Men and Small Boys at Sundown," TS, corrected,1950 (Carton 60, Folder 12)
    - The Adventures of Pvt. Alexander Macedonia: TS, 2 copies,1943 (Carton 60, Folder 13)
    - The Adventures of Pvt. Alexander Macedonia: Titled "Alexander the Great and the Princess Fatma," TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected ,n.d. (Carton 60, Folder 14)
    - The Adventures of Pvt. Alexander Macedonia: TS carbons, corrected, 3 copies,1962 (Carton 60, Folder 15)
    - After Sadness Laughter: TS, corrected,1940 (Carton 60, Folder 16)
    - The Agony of Little Nations: TS, 2 copies; TS carbon, 2 copies,1940 (Carton 60, Folder 17)
    - Ah-Ha, The Cat Saw the Mouse: Tearsheet; galley,1965 (Carton 60, Folder 18)
    - The Album of Success: TS, corrected; TS carbons, 2 copies; tearsheet,1954 (Carton 60, Folder 19)
    - Alive: TS carbon; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 60, Folder 20)
    - Almass: TS; TS carbon,1966 (Carton 60, Folder 21)
    - American Dream: TS, corrected, 2 copies; TS carbon,1934 (Carton 60, Folder 22)
    - Amerikanian: TS; photocopy,1973 (Carton 60, Folder 23)
    - "...And All Like That There: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 60, Folder 24)
    - Anything You Say: Tearsheet,1938 (Carton 60, Folder 25)
    - Aram Saectyujkfogl: TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected,1952 (Carton 60, Folder 26)
    - Aram Saectyujkfogl: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 60, Folder 27)
    - Aram Saectyujkfogl: Galleys, annotated; tearsheet,1955 (Carton 60, Folder 28)
    - The Armenian and the Armenian: TS,1935 (Carton 60, Folder 29)
    - The Armenian Mouse: Titled "The Mouse Who Was a Man," TS, corrected,1963 (Carton 60, Folder 30)
    - The Armenian Mouse: Titled "The Mouse Who Was a Man," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 60, Folder 31)
    - The Armenian Mouse: TS, corrected and annotated,1964 (Carton 60, Folder 32)
    - The Armenian Mouse: Galleys; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 60, Folder 33)
    - The Armenian Writers: A Short Story: TS, corrected; tearsheet,1954 (Carton 60, Folder 34)
    - The Art of Writing, or The Sneak in the Arena: TS, corrected; TS carbons, corrected, 2 copies,1949 (Carton 60, Folder 35)
    - Artists and Other Rats: TS, corrected; tearsheet,1935 (Carton 60, Folder 36)
    - The Ashtree Talkers: Titled "Rollicking Ups and Rotten Downs of 1973," TS,1973 (Carton 60, Folder 37)
    - The Ashtree Talkers: Titled "Sam Asparagus and the Two Old Wanderers," mimeo; photocopy, corrected,1973 (Carton 60, Folder 38)
    - The Ashtree Talkers: TS photocopy, corrected,1974 (Carton 60, Folder 39)
    - The Assassination: TS, corrected; TS carbons, 2 copies,1964 (Carton 60, Folder 40)
    - The Assassination: Titled "If You Were President, What Would You Do," TS carbon, corrected,1971 (Carton 60, Folder 41)
    - The Assyrian: TS, corrected, 2 copies,1949 (Carton 60, Folder 42)
    - The Assyrian: Tearsheet in French,1950 (Carton 60, Folder 43)
    - At the Chop Suey Joint on Larkin Street at Two Thirty in the Morning: TS, corrected,1937 (Carton 60, Folder 44)
    - Axis: TS, corrected,1939 (Carton 60, Folder 45)
    - Babe: TS, corrected,1937 (Carton 60, Folder 46)
    - Back in a Little Summertime Business in Orosi, Biola and Kerman Again: Titled " A Little Watermelon Business in Biola," TS, corrected; TS carbons, 2 copies,1966 (Carton 60, Folder 47)
    - Back in a Little Summertime Business in Orosi, Biola and Kerman Again: TS carbon, corrected; mimeo,1971 (Carton 60, Folder 48)
    - Banks as Robbers: How They Stole My Time: Titled "Beware of Bank Robbery," TS; TS carbon, corrected,1976 (Carton 60, Folder 49)
    - Banks as Robbers: How They Stole My Time: Galleys,1976 (Carton 60, Folder 50)
    - Banks as Robbers: How They Stole My Time: Titled "The Rewards of Bank Robbery," Tearsheet,1976 (Carton 60, Folder 51)
    - Banks as Robbers: How They Stole My Time: Tearsheets, 2 copies,1976 (Carton 60, Folder 52)
    - The Beale St. Traveler: Titled "Beale St," TS,1936 (Carton 61, Folder 1)
    - The Beale St. Traveler: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 61, Folder 2)
    - The Beale St. Traveler: Titled "The Slot Machine," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 61, Folder 3)
    - The Beale St. Traveler: Titled "The Slot Machine," bound copy with additional material,n.d. (Carton 61, Folder 4)
    - Being Refined: TS, corrected; TS carbons, 2 copies; galleys; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 61, Folder 5)
    - Benjamin Alladena Fragile, or Going the Rounds with a Tea-Hustler: Titled "Old Ben the Tea Hustler," TS, annotated; photocopy,1974 (Carton 61, Folder 6)
    - Bepo's Debt: TS carbons, 3 copies,1943 (Carton 61, Folder 7)
    - Beware of the Dog: TS, corrected,1940 (Carton 61, Folder 8)
    - Big City Blues: Tearsheet,1937 (Carton 61, Folder 9)
    - The Big Emptiness: TS,1938 (Carton 61, Folder 10)
    - The Big Midget and A Lady: Tearsheet; photocopy,1928 (Carton 61, Folder 11)
    - The Big Room Up Front: Titled "Ach Du Lieber Augustine," TS, corrected; notes,1948 (Carton 61, Folder 12)
    - The Big Room Up Front: Titled "An Unimportant Fire at the Europa Hotel," TS carbon; tearsheet,1948 (Carton 61, Folder 13)
    - The Biggest Watermelon Anybody Ever Saw: Titled "The Watermelon Eaters," TS, corrected; TS carbon,1964 (Carton 61, Folder 14)
    - The Biggest Watermelon Anybody Ever Saw: Titled "The Watermelon Eaters," galleys, 2 copies; tearsheet,1965 (Carton 61, Folder 15)
    - Bill McGee's Brother: TS, corrected; TS carbon; galleys; tearsheet,1950 (Carton 61, Folder 16)
    - Black Kitten: Tearsheet,1934 (Carton 61, Folder 17)
    - Boom Bang: Tearsheet,1965 (Carton 61, Folder 18)
    - Boy: TS,1973 (Carton 61, Folder 19)
    - The Boy from Coalinga: TS, corrected; tearsheet,1936 (Carton 61, Folder 20)
    - The Boy from Kingsburg :TS, corrected,1936 (Carton 61, Folder 21)
    - Boy O Boy O Boy, O Boy: Tearsheet,1935 (Carton 61, Folder 22)
    - The Boy Who Was Different: Tearsheet; galley,1950 (Carton 61, Folder 23)
    - The Boy With the Big Nose: Galleys; photocopy; tearsheet,n.d. (Carton 61, Folder 24)
    - The Brigadier General Who Won: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1964 (Carton 61, Folder 25)
    - The Brothers and the Sisters: TS, corrected,1937 (Carton 61, Folder 26)
    - California: TS, corrected,1937 (Carton 61, Folder 27)
    - Catalogue Carter the World's Champion Martyr: TS, corrected,1939 (Carton 61, Folder 28)
    - The Celebrated Bank Holiday of August,1944: TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected (Carton 61, Folder 29)
      1944
    - The Chair: TS, corrected,1955 (Carton 61, Folder 30)
    - Champagne for Everybody: TS, 2 copies; TS carbon, 2 copies,1938 (Carton 61, Folder 31)
    - The Christmas Day Christmas Tree: TS, corrected,1949 (Carton 61, Folder 32)
    - Cinema-City Romance: TS, corrected; TS carbon,1939 (Carton 61, Folder 33)
    - The Circus: TS, corrected,1938 (Carton 61, Folder 34)
    - The College Graduate: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 61, Folder 35)
    - Comma, I: TS, corrected,1931 (Carton 61, Folder 36)
    - The Competition: TS, corrected,1956 (Carton 61, Folder 37)
    - Corduroy Pants: TS, corrected,1936 (Carton 61, Folder 38)
    - The Country: TS, corrected,1940 (Carton 61, Folder 39)